Guide to the Irish Echo Photographs AIA.045
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII. Individuals, circa 1960-2004; 6.70 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 3 card boxes, 3 manuscript boxes, 1 oversized flat box, and 1 half manuscript box
  - "O", circa 1970s-2004, undated (Box 13, Folder 24, Box 18, Folder 42, Oversize 21, Folder 13, Box 27, Folder 12)
  - O'Connor, John Cardinal, 1985-1991, 1999, undated (Box 13, Folder 25, Oversize 21, Folder 14, Box 34, Folder 15)
  - O'Donnell, John "Kerry", 1994, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - O'Dwyer, Brian, 1995-1996, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - O'Fiatch, Cardinal Tomas, 1994, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - O'Hara, Maureen, 1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - O'Reilly, Patricia, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - O'Reilly, Tony, 1988, 1993-1997, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - O'Reilly, Tony, Gay Mitchell, Bill McCann of Price Waterhouse, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - "P", 1977, 1988-1999, 2001, undated (Box 13, Folder 32, Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Pearson, Noel (Producer), 1992-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 33, Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Phelan, Margaret, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Princess Grace of Monaco, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - "Q", 1986, 1988, 1991, undated (Box 13, Folder 35, Box 27, Folder 15)
  - "R", circa 1980-1982, 1987-1996, undated (Box 13, Folder 36, Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Roarty, Michael J., 1988, undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Roberts, Julia, undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Rooney, Dan, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - "S", circa 1970s, 1981, 1986-2000, undated (Box 13, Folder 39, Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Sheehan, Deninis, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Sheen, Bishop Fulton J., 1968, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Sheeran, Edward, 1996, undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Smythe, Jimmy, undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Sweeney, John, 1985, 1987, undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - "T", 1985-1988, 1992-2002, undated (Box 13, Folder 44, Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Unidentified, circa 1970-2004, undated (Box 20, Folder 37, Box 19, Folder 1-20, Box 18, Folder 43-44, Box 13, Folder 45-47, Box 27, Folder 21-22, Box 28, Folder 1-2, Box 31, Folder 6, Box 32, Folder 35, Box 33, Folder 28, Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified - Birthday Party, undated (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Unidentified - Child with Santa Claus, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Unidentified - Couple, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Unidentified - Mother/Daughter in Garden, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - "V", 1994-1995, undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - "W," "X," "Y" and "Z", 1982, 1988-1992, undated (Box 13, Folder 49, Box 27, Folder 20)